binweevils.com 2009-08-31

# Bin Weevils - Information

About Bin Weevils Limited

Bin Weevils was formed as a 50/50 joint venture between Nickelodeon UK and Prism Entertainment

This year the company Bin Weevils Limited was formed and is a Joint Venture between: 

> **Prism Entertainment** (Producers and Content creators) - [www.prismentertainment.co.uk](http://www.prismentertainment.co.uk/)

A leading digital and online agency, specialising in communicating and connecting with a range of consumer audiences  
Creates, designs and then builds websites and the various elements of online advertising campaigns  
6 years experience in the provision of progressive and entertaining online solutions to numerous key brands

> **Nickelodeon UK** (Broadcast, Marketing and Financial backer) - [www.nick.co.uk](http://www.nick.co.uk/)

Nickelodeon UK is a joint venture between MTV Networks and BSkyB  
Nickelodeon UK comprises five dedicated award-winning entertainment channels for kids aged 2 to 12  
In addition, each channel is complemented by red button games and interactive websites, which are home to thriving online message boards and communities 

**CEG (Creative Entertainment Group)** (Financial & Strategic investor) - [www.ceg-events.com](http://www.ceg-events.com/)

CEG is a recent investor into Bin Weevils, for more information about CEG, please visit their website. 

These Terms and Conditions apply to UK residents only

**Registration:**  
1\. If you are under 13 and register an account you are representing (i.e. making a promise) that you have consent from your parents / guardian to use Bin Weevils in accordance with our terms and conditions and privacy policy. We reserve the right to permanently ban any account if we are not satisfied that such consent has been given.

2\. If we are notified by a parent that their child has lied about their age when registering on Bin Weevils, we will terminate the account provided we have confirmation which satisfies us that the reporting person is indeed the parent or guardian.

3\. Before registering and playing on Bin Weevils, you should read the guides found in our [Parents section](http://www.binweevils.com/parents/). It is particularly important to read the [Safety Guide](http://www.binweevils.com/parents/safety.html) and the [Safety Rules](http://www.binweevils.com/parents/rules.html). 

**  
BIN WEEVILS COMPETITION TERMS AND CONDITIONS  
**Bin Weevils Limited of 220 Latimer Road, London W10 6QY is the promoter of the Competition (Promoter). 

Please read the following rules carefully. 

These standard competition terms and conditions (“Terms And Conditions”) will apply to all of the Promoter’s competitions unless otherwise stated.

Depending on the nature of the competition, it may be necessary to have additional terms and conditions (“Additional Terms and Conditions”), which will take priority over these Terms And Conditions. 

The Promoter shall notify the entrants of any Additional Terms and Conditions that may apply to a competition.

Entrants may enter the competition by following the directions given in respect of each competition. 

1\. To enter all competitions you must be aged 16 years or under and be residents of the UK and Eire. 

2\. All entrants must obtain parental consent prior to entering competitions.

3\. We may require proof of eligibility which may include the entrant to submit birth certificates or other proof of elibility.

4\. Entrants must provide the details requested by the Promoter, which may include entrant’s name, date of birth, age, address (including postcode), telephone number and/or email address. 

5\. The competition is entered online on the Bin Weevils site and nowhere else.

6\. This competition is not open to employees (or members of their immediate families) of Bin Weevils Limited, or members of their immediate families of Prism Entertainment & Creative Entertainment Group. 

7\. The Promoter is not responsible for any and all expenses in connection with the prize including but not limited to transportation. 

8\. No purchase necessary.

9\. Only one entry per household per competition 

10\. Any personal information (entrant’s name, age, address, telephone number and/or email address will be used solely in connection with this competition and will not be disclosed to any third party, except for the purpose of fulfilling the prize where applicable. Any personal information held by the Promoter in respect of the competition will be held on record for a short period for the purpose of ensuring fulfilment of the competition. 

11\. The winner(s) will be selected at random by Bin Weevils Limited from correct and eligible entries. Their decision is final and no correspondence will be entered in to over this decision.

12\. Closing Date: The closing date shall be the date and/or time given in the instructions for the competition and unless otherwise stated  
We will not enter into any correspondence regarding entries received after this date. No responsibility is accepted for late or lost entries due to the internet or other. Proof of sending is not proof of receipt. 

13\. For question and answer competitions, the winner will have answered the question correctly and will be the first entry randomly drawn after the closing date from all the correct entries received.  
For skills based competitions, such as designing and/or story writing competitions or performing challenges, the winner will have successfully completed the required skills based task and will be the person whom the Promoter judges deem to have performed such task the best from all the entries received. The Promoter’s decision is final. 

14\. In the event that the Promoter cannot for any reason contact the winner within 7 days of the first draw then the promoter reserves the right to randomly draw another set of winners. 

15\. If you do not claim your prize within 7 days we reserve the right to offer the prize to another successful entrant whose name is next drawn at random. 

16\. You can find out who won by sending a stamped addressed envelope to Bin Weevils Limited, 220 Latimer Road, London, W10 6QY after the competition closing date. 

17\. The prize and quantities are stated on the individual competitions.

18\. No part of the prize is exchangeable for cash or any other prize. However we reserve the right to award a substitute prize of equal value. No cash alternatives will be offered. 

19\. By entering the competition, the winners of any prize agree to participate in such promotional activities and feature in such promotional material as Bin Weevils may require. 

20\. If circumstances arise outside of our control we reserve the right to cancel the competition at any stage. 

21\. The Promoter is committed to a strict privacy policy. 

22\. This competition is being run by Bin Weevils Limited of 220, Latimer Road, London, W10 6QY (the “Promoter”).

23\. These competition Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and constructed in accordance with the laws of England and Wales and the courts of England shall have exclusive jurisdiction in relation to any disputes arising.

**King of the Bin competition:**  
1\. Entrants enter the King of the Bin competition by playing games and doing activities on the Bin Weevils web site. Costs to enter the competition via the Internet may vary so please check with your network operator for current charges. Entrants should seek the permission of the person paying the bill before entering.

2\. The closing date for entries is Midnight on Sunday every week. For the foreseeable future.

3\. This competition is open to residents of the UK aged sixteen (16) and under, excluding employees and immediate relatives of employees of Bin Weevils Limited (the “Producer”) and/or of their respective parents, subsidiaries or affiliated companies or any other person connected with this competition. Entrants must obtain parental consent prior to entering this competition.

4\. The Bin Weevil with the highest score will be contacted via e-mail and asked to supply name, age, address, (including postcode), and possibly telephone number. Entrants MUST obtain permission from their parents prior to sending these details. An employee of Bin Weevils Limited will verify their prize claim and may interview the prospective winner.

5\. There can only be 1 winner per household per month. This is to give other people the opportunity to win a prize within that 1 month period.

6\. The prize will be as listed on the prize page shown on the website for the week in question.  
For the avoidance of doubt, the players should view the prize page on the Bin Weevils Site to see what that weekly prize is. 

7\. The prize will be posted to the winner only when all the criteria listed above have been complied. The prize fulfillment shall be at the sole discretion of the Producer. Please allow up to 28 days for delivery. 

8\. In the event that the Producer cannot for any reason contact the selected winner 1 month after the winner has been announced the producer reserves the right to withdraw the prize.

9\. The judge’s decision is final. No correspondence will be entered into.

10\. The Producer reserves the right to select an alternative winner in the event that the Promoter has reasonable grounds for believing that the selected winner has contravened any of these Terms and Conditions of entry.

11\. The winner maybe required to provide a parent’s or legal guardian’s signature as written acknowledgement of acceptance of all Terms and Conditions of the competition prior to receiving the prize.

12\. No responsibility can be accepted for prizes lost, delayed, misdirected, damaged or undelivered. The Producer shall not be responsible for technical errors in telecommunications networks, Internet access or otherwise preventing entry to any competition. 

13\. The prize is as stated and is non-transferable. No cash alternatives will be offered. If due to circumstances beyond the Producers control the Producer is unable to provide the stated prize, the Producer reserves the right to award a substitute prize of equal value. All prizes are subject to the additional terms and conditions of the Event organizer including any terms and conditions in relation to entrance to the Event. 

14\. No purchase necessary. 

15\. By entering the competition, entrants acknowledge that they may be required to be used in publicity without further consent or payment. Such publicity may include without limitation the entrant’s name and/or likeness, voice, photographs and/or video footage of the entrant, biographical information provided by the entrants/winner and/or the winner’s guests and/or any statement made by them concerning the competition and/or the prize. Entrants agree that any or all such elements may be used by the Producer in any and all media in perpetuity throughout the world as the Producer in its sole discretion sees fit. 

16\. The Producer shall not be liable to the winner and/or any guests and/or parents/legal guardians for any loss or damage howsoever caused (whether in contract, tort or statutory duty or otherwise) arising out of or in connection with the competition and/or prize other than death or personal injury caused by negligence of the Producer and/or the Producer personnel and/or deceit or fraud by Producer and/or Producer personnel. 

17\. The Producer shall not be liable for any delay in performing or partial or total failure to perform any of its obligations to the winner (and/or any guests) under these competition Terms and Conditions if such delay or failure is caused by circumstances beyond its reasonable control including without limitation delays, changes, disruptions, cancellations, diversions or substitutions howsoever caused including without limitation as a result of war, terrorist action or threatened terrorist action, strikes, hostilities, civil commotions, accidents, fire, flood or natural catastrophes including where any of the above arise without limitation out of or in connection with (i) the activities of the Event organizers; (ii) any form of transportation (including but not limited to flights, trains, coaches, buses, ferries, taxis or cars); and/or (iii) by third parties providing accommodation that may be included in the prize. For the avoidance of doubt, the winner (and/or any guests and/or parents/legal guardians) shall be solely liable for any additional costs incurred as a result.

18\. The name of the winner can be obtained by sending a stamped addressed envelope to King of the Bin Competition Winner (Week No), Bin Weevils Limited, 220 Latimer Road, London, W10 6QY , for one (1) month after the competition closes.

19\. Any personal information, including without limitation, the entrant's name, age, address (including postcode), telephone number and/or email address will be used solely in connection with this competition and will not be disclosed to any third party, except for the purpose of fulfilling the prize where applicable. Any personal information held by the Promoter in respect of any competition will be held on record for a short period for the purpose of ensuring fulfillment of the competition and then destroyed.

20\. All entrants agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions, which may be amended or varied at any time by the Promoter on notice.

21\. These competition Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of England and Wales and the courts of England shall have exclusive jurisdiction in relation to any disputes arising there from.

22\. Bin Weevils Limited, 220 Latimer Road, London W10 6QY

Bin Weevils is the place in cyberspace where kids can play games, enter competitions, win prizes, chat to friends and watch favourite cartoons. Bin Weevils believes in the power of kids and we urge both them and their parents to use and enjoy our Site. Whilst we encourage the interactive nature of online media, we strive to educate parents and kids about how to appropriately safeguard their privacy when travelling on the web. Our information collection practices are described below. We urge kids to check with their parents before entering any information on any website and we urge parents to discuss with their kids restrictions regarding the online release of personal information to anyone they don't know. 

What Information Is Collected?

At Bin Weevils Limited, it is our policy to create website content which requires minimum collection of information from our visitors. Generally, Bin Weevils limits collection of information to what is known as non-personally identifiable information (e.g. first name, age, gender, city or town). This information is collected so kids can participate in activities without giving out unnecessary personal information. Where we need extra information, e.g. kids/'parents' email addresses, telephone numbers (as explained below) to run competitions or to offer extra on-line activities, we let kids know the reason for which we are collecting the information and what we will do with it. We do not as a condition to a kid's participation in any of our on-line activity require the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary. 

The data controller for the purposes of UK data protection legislation is Bin Weevils Limited (“we” or “us” or “our”). The ways we collect user’s (“you” or “your” or “user”) personal information and how we use it on the Site are as follows:

1\. Registration 

The main way we collect personally identifiable information is through our registration process. In order to take part in our registered member activities, we only ask kids to submit their age and email address. If the child is under 12, then we also ask for their parents/guardians email so we can also send them a confirmation email. We ask each kid if they wish to opt-in to receiving emails from us as part of our activities for registered members e.g. our newsletter. We remind them to ask a parent/guardian for permission first. The information is used to allow kids to take part in registered member activities such as message boards, newsletters, any special member competitions and send e-cards. Registered kids can unsubscribe at any time. To unsubscribe, please contact us at the following email address: help@binweevils.com. 

All such personal information collected during the registration process is used only for the purpose of providing kids with access to our registered member activities. It is not currently our policy to use such information for general marketing purposes or to share such information with third parties (except in relation to competitions as set out below or where we are required to do so by law or in the context of a business transfer). Should our policy on this change, we will let you know and give you the choice to be included. 

We do not obtain or require disclosure of sensitive personal data (such as ethnic origin or religion) but if you choose to provide us with such sensitive personal data, we may assume such sensitive personal data is provided with your express consent for processing by us for the purposes for which such personal data was provided by you unless otherwise notified by you to us in writing at the following email address: help@binweevils.com . 

2\. Competitions

We offer the opportunity for all kids to enter competitions on-line. In order to run competitions and send out prizes, it is necessary to collect some personally identifiable information from kids. This can include name, address and telephone number. As a matter of policy, we keep such information only for the purposes of administering the competition and do not disclose such information to third parties except where necessary to fulfill the prizes (e.g. it may be shared with fulfillment houses for processing purposes). We may from time to time offer competitions sponsored by third party businesses and may share entrant information with such businesses in order to fulfill the competition only. We will provide potential entrants with the opportunity to opt-in to such third party sponsored competitions. Once a competition is finished, we will delete any personal information collected via on-line entry forms from our systems and it is not kept for any longer than is necessary. 

3\. Electronic Cards 

We may give kids the option to send "electronic card " to their friends. We do not collect our visitors' full names, but we do collect email addresses during this process in order to inform the user that their e-card has been read. We also ask users to submit their friends' email addresses so we can send them these e-cards. We think it would be disproportionate to inform user’s friend(s) about our privacy policy and how we will be using their personal data beforehand because it would spoil the surprise of receiving the friend’s electronic card. However, we can reassure users that this data is not transferred to a third party or used for marketing purposes and it is not kept for any longer than is necessary. 

4\. Feedback

We provide kids with the opportunity to email us with their opinions and comments. We request no personally identifiable information unless the kid indicates that he or she wants us to reply. In these circumstances, we ask for a first name and email address. This information is used solely by us in order to give requested feedback and is then deleted from our system periodically. 

5\. Cookies and Log Data

Cookies are information files that your web browser places on the hard drive of your computer when you visit certain websites. We are able to access only the cookies that our Site places on your computer and we are only able to determine the type of computer operating system and browser that you are using. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read information from a user's hard drive. Cookies allow websites to "remember" users activities on a website as well as users visits to a website. At binweevils.com, cookies are used to determine the number of unique visitors to our Site over a given period. We do not store any personal information in the cookies nor do we link or combine information collected through cookies to any personal information submitted by users when participating in our activities. We collect this information in order to improve access to our content based on our visitors' browsers and operating system types to make our content available to as many kids as possible. You can, of course, disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. 

Log data collected on web servers within our control also supplies us with non-personally identifiable information about the number of visits to different pages on our Site. We use this information only for improving our Site. We do not link the "log data" collected to personally identifiable information submitted by users when participating in our activities. 

The information collected through cookies and log data may be passed to our Research Department or to third party advertisers or business partners. 

If you do not wish us to use cookies for the purposes explained above, please inform us in writing at the following email address: help@binweevils.com .

6\. Transfer of Personal Data

We may also transfer your personal data collected to any country, including countries outside the European Economic Area, for any of the purposes described above. Your provision of personal data to us through use of this Site is understood by us to constitute consent to such transfer unless you inform us of your wish not to transfer your personal data in this manner at the following email address: help@binweevils.com .

7\. Monitoring of Communications

We may record or monitor your telephone conversations and email correspondence with our staff for security, compliance with the law, training purposes and to maintain and improve the quality of our services.

8\. Security

We have taken steps to ensure that all personally identifiable information that we collect is secure, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers as well as electronic security systems and password protections, which guard against unauthorised access. 

9\. Agents

The personally identifiable information provided to binweevils.com may be transferred, disclosed or shared with third parties who may be engaged by us as data processors to specifically to handle and deliver certain activities (e.g. message boards, competitions, e-cards, newsletters, advisory board, communities) and perform other technical and processing functions, such as sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from registration lists, programming, providing services to our users, or otherwise operating our Site. They have access to personal information needed to perform their processing functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

10\. Third party websites

We provide a "bumper page" when linking from our Site to an advertiser's site, which lets kids know they are going to an advertiser's site and reminds them not to give out information online without getting permission from their parents. Kids and their parents should be aware that other sites have different policies on collection of information to us, so it is important to check their Privacy Policies before submitting any personally identifiable information. 

11\. Business Transfers

In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are transferred or sold to another business, you agree that we may transfer any of your personally identifiable information to the acquiring business.

12\. Questions/Concerns?

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our privacy policy and/or practices, please contact us at the following email address: help@binweevils.com . 

Alternatively you can write to: 

Standards and Practices  
Bin Weevils Limited   
220 Latimer Road   
LONDON  
W10 6QY

The Bin Weevils Clubs allows users to gain exclusive access to certain areas within the bin. They will also receive exclusive newsletters with information about that particular club. Users will be able to unsubscribe when they receive a newsletter.   
More information will be added here as more clubs are made.
